nudesonline.com 2010-03-15

# PRIVACY POLICY

**PRIVACY POLICY**

Online Privacy is a constantly evolving matter and our company takes every effort to maintain up to date and effective online privacy standards and practices. 

We are committed to respecting your online privacy and recognize your need for appropriate protection and management of any personally identifiable information you share with us.

**Choice**   
Visiting our website in no way requires you to give us any personal information.  When you become a member, you are choosing to give us your information and we are committed to keeping your information private and secure in every manner possible.

**What kind of information  is collected** **  
** When you join our web site as a paying member, you are asked to provide such information as, but not limited to, your name, address, email, & username and password When users request pages from our server, our Web server automatically   
collects some information about the users, including their IP addresses, date and time of visit and referring URL. We also collect information regarding your use of our site through the use of cookies. If you send us personal correspondence, such as emails or letters, we may collect such information into a file specific   
to you. 

**Sharing of Information**  
We do not, and will not, distribute, rent or sell any personally identifiable information to third parties without your express consent,  unless requested via a subpoena, court order, or local, state, federal or international law enforcement request. 

**Information Usage**  
We use your information in order to process your credit card payment, to facilitate your viewing of our web site and to communicate with you. We also use this information to compile broad demographic and web site usage information about our users in general that does not contain anything that could be used to   
identify you personally. We use your email address to send occasional email newsletters and promotional email to you about services and products offered by us or by other parties which we feel may be of interest to you. We will not spam you and honor all removal requests immediately. 

**Age**   
We do not allow any visitors under the age of 18, hence no information is collected on anyone under the age of 18.

**3rd Party Links  
**Our Website contains links to other sites produced by us as well as websites operated by unrelated third parties. Please note that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party websites. We encourage you to be aware of this when your leave our Website and to read the privacy policies of every website that collects personally identifiable information from you. The Privacy Policy applies only to this Website.

**Information Security**  
We take reasonable precautions to maintain the security of any information obtained from and about you. We provide you with a secure web page through which to submit your billing information when you join the membership portion of our web site. 

**Contacting Us** **  
** Site owner recognizes the importance of protecting your privacy. If you have any questions about this Privacy Statement, the practices of this web site or your dealings with this site, please contact us by mail at [helpdesk@flashcash.com](mailto:helpdesk@flashcash.com)
